<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neil Pareddy</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Neil Pareddy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Python in R</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>Using Python in SDS348 We’ve imported python code into RMarkdown files, such as this one. We used reticulate to allow R and python to talk to each other in python code chunks. Below is some work from HW assignments.
The following is my solution to the problem: Write a function that takes a string of nucleotides as input and returns a dictionary with all 3-mers present in that string, and the number of times that each 3-mer occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Buzzfeed had published an article titled, “The Agriculture Department Hired More Than 50 Political Appointees. They All Say They’re White.,” wherein they featured an analysis regarding the disparency of minority representation between Senior Executives and Political Staff. To corroberate this theory, the datasets used in Project 1 come form the Office of Personnel Management’s FedScope tool. The ethnic diversity data comes from FedScope’s “Diversity Cubes”, and the gender data is come from the “Employment Cubes”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling Instructions A knitted R Markdown document (as a PDF) and the raw R Markdown file (as .Rmd) should both be submitted to Canvas by 11:59pm on 11/24/2019. These two documents will be graded jointly, so they must be consistent (i.e., don’t change the R Markdown file without also updating the knitted document). Knit an html copy too, for later! In the .Rmd file for Project 2, you can copy the first code-chunk into your project .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>